Finding Aid for the Doris Ann Dudney Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Doris Ann Dudney Collection
Undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0822
.42 linear_feet
Biographical Note
Doris Ann Dudney was born in 1934 in Tampa, Florida and died in 2013. She attended Vanderbilt University as an undergraduate where she double majored in economics and mathematics. While at Vanderbilt, Dudney became a member of the sorority of Kappa Delta in 1951. Following graduation, Dudney was admitted to Vanderbilt Law School where she became the first female editor-in-chief of the Vanderbilt Law Review, where she published nine issues between 1955-1956. Furthermore, Dudney was the recipient of the Law School excellence scholarship and graduated with the Founder’s Medal in 1956.
Ms. Dudney then returned to Florida to practice as an independent attorney and later, a Senior Law Clerk for the Second District Court of Appeals. She served as Chairman of the Economics of Law Practice Committee for the Florida Bar and District 11 Governor of Zonta International.
Scope and Content Note
This collection is composed of one Hollinger box with seven folders. Within the collection is a biography of Dudney, her Kappa Delta initiation certificate, her notes from law school, her license to practice law in Florida, correspondence from both her and her family, and an article by Opal S. Dudney.
- Doris Ann Dudney Biography (Folder 1)
- Kappa Delta Sorority Certificate (Folder 2)
- Notes from Law School (Folder 3)
- Supreme Court of Florida Attorney License (Folder 4)
- Correspondence (Folder 5)
- Letter from a young Doris to her father
- Letter to Opal Laine, April 28th, 1925
- Letter to Mr. Stan Dudney, Nov. 9th, 1940
- Letter to Mr. Stan Dudney, Nov. 9th, 1940
- Letter from Fred Dudney, Nov. 20th, 1940
- Letter to Master Stan Dudney, Nov. 24, 1940
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, Jan. 16, 1941
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, Jan. 18, 1941
- Fuel Oil Ration Coupon for Fred S. Dudney, Jan. 28, 1942
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, May 16th, 1943
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, May 19th, 1943
- Correspondence (Folder 6)
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, June, 1945
- Letter to Opal, May 11, 1946
- Letter from Fred Dudney, June 4, 1946
- Letter to the Dudneys, Sept. 11th, 1950
- Letter to Mr. and Mrs. Dudney, Oct. 5th, 1950
- Letter to Mr. and Mrs. Dudney, Oct. 26th, 1950
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, Oct. 30th, 1950
- Letter to Mr. and Mrs. Dudney, Jan. 24th, 1951
- Letter to Mrs. Dudney, Mar. 17th, 1951
- Letter to Mrs. Opal Dudney, Mar. 27th, 1951
- Opal S. Dudney Article (Folder 7)